‪PREVIOUSLY ON ‪CHOSEN HOME
An animal lover
who's gentle-hearted and gay,
Genichi Hatano,
falls in love.
His crush is a fellow gay man
and middle school teacher, Saku Sakuta.
I broke up with my partner
and ended our cohabitation.
I was spending the night in my car.
Genichi wishes for Saku’s happiness.
What do you think about buying a house?
Maybe buying a house could be the "clamp".
Do as you like.
But Saku has a problematic student.
Hotaru Kusunoki.
She's a third-year middle schooler
who hangs around the red light district.
This is my dad.
Yes, he's my dad!
I'm begging you.
For some reason, Hotaru wants him
to pretend to be her dad.
With the suitcase buried in the yard,
Hotaru decides to pull off
the gamble of her lifetime.
- What the?
- Here is 30 million yen.
You want a house, right?
I will… buy you.
- What do you mean, buy?
- With this money.
- Me, that is?
- Yes.
What do you mean?
I'm saying I'll give you this money.
You then use it to buy a house,
but in return, I want you
to pretend to be my dad.
- I don't get it.
- Like I said--
First of all, what's this money?
- Whose is it?
- Ours.
Your mom. Where is she now?
Can't you ask your dad from the other day?
I can tell you’ve got
your reasons in a way.
But you should talk to your teac--
I'm saying I don't want to!
Why not?
I’m not asking you
to become my real parent.
Just act the part when it’s needed.
Come on now.
Do you know what you're saying?
It's not something I can just do.
Why are you alone?
At least tell me the reason.
And this money.
Give me a proper explanation, okay?
With this much, we could buy
a nice big house!
One where the dogs could run around!
Wouldn’t that be fun?
Hey, stop it. Let's put this away, yeah?
And a big bath
where you can splash around!
- We don’t need that kind of house.
- Then what kind do you want?
I’m buying you,
so pick any house you like.
Coming! Please wait a moment.
Hey, careful.
- Yes?
- Hello. Delivery service.
Please sign here.
- Thank you.
These are shishamo fish
from my parents in Hokkaido.
They always send me tons
around this time of year.
Oh yeah?
Want some? I'll share it with you.
Thank you.
What do you usually eat?
You live alone, right?
- I just eat whatever.
- What about money? Your living expenses?
- I'm fine.
- Really?
- Thank you for this.
- Huh?
- So, I’ll be counting on you.
- Wait, hey, your--
- Thank you for having me.
- What?
SHISHAMO WITH ROE
There. We're good to go.
Sorry, give me a second.
What did I do with it?
Where is it?
Looking for something?
- No way!
- No way?
- Do you need some help?
- No, thank you.
A sock, huh?
They usually fall between the washer
and the wall, you know.
Well, I don't have a house.
"Between the washer and the wall," sure.
Um, about Yoshida…
Have you spoken to Hotaru
about her future?
She'd better hand in
her career sheet soon.
I'll just wear this one.
Man, you're such a nuis--
Someone was camping out in their car,
so I told them off.
- Got it.
- I'll be on my way now.
Thank you for your work.
Something happened?
Someone was camping out
in their car in the lot.
Security reported
that he gave them a warning.
I hope they take it well though.
Right.
LIST OF CAR CAMPING SPOTS IN TOKYO
I came to hand in the class journal.
Thanks.
- Bye.
- Wait!
Is he okay? I mean, your dad.
What do you mean?
With stuff.
What stuff?
Never mind.
If he's okay, then it's all good.
Are you okay? Your socks don't match.
Bye.
TO KUSUNOKI. I’VE LIKED YOU
FOR A LONG TIME
PLEASE MEET ME BEHIND THE GYM
AFTER SCHOOL ON MONDAY
How about homework?
GAS BILL
TO KUSUNOKI
I’VE LIKED YOU FOR A LONG TIME…
DAD
INOKASHIRA APARTMENTS
- Welcome back.
- I'm back.
How's the unit?
It's old, so I'm a little concerned.
- Are you fine with it?
- Yes.
I’m content just having
a roof over my head.
I'm back, Banana.
Sorry, I need you to make way.
SAKUTA
This is Hatano speaking.
This is Sakuta.
- Is everything okay?
- What?
The guard told you off
about sleeping in your car, right?
More importantly, regarding Hotaru…
- Are you listening?
- Yes.
Three months ago,
the police, Hotaru, and I
had a session.
This time, we’d like her dad to join us.
Wait, the police?
The officer-in-charge is called Mr. Matsu.
You haven't met him before, right?
We’d like to go over the incident,
your current situation as her dad,
and other related matters.
When would be a good time for you?
Well…
How about next Tuesday?
Maybe around 6 p.m.?
- Okay.
- See you then.
- Thank you.
- See you.
YOSHIDA: CAN WE MEET THIS WEEKEND?
- Oh, Hotaru!
- Hey.
We're doing something fun!
Let me in on it.
We’re doing a fake press conference!
Which celebrity
does your fiancé look like?
- He's just some old guy.
- Did you hear that?
What made you decide to get married?
- Huh? Marriage?!
- Well…
- It's got to be his financial stability.
- Wait, are you getting married, Nacchi?
Of course not!
Thank goodness.
- You scared me!
- Did you believe it?
- Tell us. Did you?
- Shut up!
An older guy she got along well with
offered her a prenuptial agreement.
Or so she said.
What's that?
I guess it's like a promise to marry
or something?
A "We’ll get married someday,
so let’s do our best" type of agreement.
- Cheers!
- Do your best!
Wait…
If I sign the agreement,
he’ll give me 50,000 yen every month.
I’ll take all the money I can,
and once it gets annoying,
I'll just abandon him.
- You're a genius!
- Genius idea!
Hi-five!
Look at this!
"For indecent acts with a minor,
a man was arrested…"
If it's proven the guy had
a prenuptial agreement with the girl
and they were in
an engagement-like relationship,
it may not be considered
a violation of law.
- Meaning?
- Even if he does something gross to you,
he might not get arrested!
- That's not good.
- Do you have the agreement with you?
No, it's with him.
What, you don't have it?
- No!
- What?
CAREER SHEET
Are you looking for Hotaru?
Yes.
She usually doesn’t come back until
late at night on the days she goes out.
You'll probably have to wait
a little longer.
Um… Do you know her situation?
‪Well,
I mean, Hotaru's circumstances.
That's a secret.
Right.
NIKOMADO
Speaking of which,
was everything okay the other day?
I heard you had trouble with some kids.
Oh, that. They were collecting coins,
so I thought they must be
really short on money.
When I asked them,
"Is there anything you want?",
they got creeped out.
Well, yeah.
It’s creepy and kinda annoying.
Really?
But I did clear the misunderstanding
with them later.
There he is. Koinobori!
Oh, just as we speak of them.
What's wrong?
- Hey, won't you marry me too?
- Me too, please!
- You too?
- No, me.
- So hard to decide…
- Please!
- Pretty please!
- How old are you, anyway?
- Well, I'm…
Sorry for interrupting.
Hello. I’m with Nikomado,
from the Niko Consultation Desk.
I heard about what happened.
So, what’s this prenuptial agreement?
Let’s go to the police together.
I don't wanna!
Hand it over!
Nicely done!
This?
That's not it.
- This!
- Yes!
Let's get out of here!
Quick!
Wait!
- Where are you going?
- Hey!
PARKING
2,000 YEN FOR THE FIRST 24 HOURS
That's so expensive!
Time to sleep.
So, I suggested we buy a house
and make it our "family glue".
Guess what? He said I'm scaring him.
He's got a point.
But the one who said "love and revolution"
and "family glue"
was you, Ms. Momose.
That really lit a fire in me!
Oh, no.
I assumed it was for the sake
of your partner.
I don’t have anyone like that.
Then, can I take it that you're here today
to join the membership?
Hang on…
Looking back,
I think I suggested the "family glue" idea
because I wanted that person to be happy.
So, I can’t actually join.
Does that mean it’s already started?
It might have already started… I think.
- Lots of things.
- Really?
You know…
- A kid…
- Wait, did you say, kid?
Your partner has a child?
It's not exactly that.
- I don’t quite understand the situation.
- Me neither.
I love parfaits.
Why all of a sudden?
To me, a parfait is life.
The cream, the fruits, the cereal.
They all stack together
to make the parfait, right?
Similarly, life is made up
of the accumulation of what we do
in the present.
If you do what you can
and what you should now,
eventually, you’ll realize
you’ve made a proper parfait.
Is that…
from Dazai or something too?
No. It's Momose's original quote.
Where is it?
- Looking for something?
- Yeah.
Have you seen a Santa-patterned sock?
- Nope.
- Maybe over there.
- Is it that important?
- I don't know.
I'm just searching for it for no reason.
Why?
For my parfait.
Welcome home. I mean, please come on in.
- Thank you for having me.
- Wear these.
Did you rearrange the place?
Well, duh. Also, those are your things.
The stuff in the bathroom…
I couldn’t tell whose was whose,
so just take yours back.
You're the type to delete all photos
after breaking up.
I throw away all the gifts too.
- I thought this was about Hatano.
- What?
Didn't he come
with the marriage registration?
Oh yeah, he did.
But seriously, don't go passing that
to randoms.
I didn't think he'd go see you.
In the end, I still don’t know
why he came.
What did you talk about?
Can’t remember much… What was it again?
He said he wanted to fall madly in love.
- He told me to buy a house.
- Huh?
He said you and I
should buy a house together,
and use that as a clamp,
so we’d always be together.
How does that work?
- I don’t know.
- He's crazy.
I know, right?
Are you done?
This is everything.
Why don't we stay together
until we can file the marriage papers?
What? You're being a creep.
- Figured.
- See you.
Thanks for having me.
See you.
Hey! Wait here.
Are you okay?
Dang it!
- Open the door!
- No, I'm fine!
- Just open the goddamn door!
- Ugh!
If you don't mind me…
Get out of the way!
It's a good thing the fire didn’t spread.
You could say that again.
I was grilling the shishamo fish,
and it exploded into flames.
Shishamo?
You've got quite the refined taste.
I shared some with her.
It came from Hokkaido.
Is that so?
Sorry, I didn’t teach her
how to cook them properly.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
It’s totally fine,
but I don’t get any shishamo, huh?
Huh?
I see how it is.
Shishamo from Hokkaido, huh?
That's cool. It must be good shishamo.
- Maybe it's karafuto shishamo.
- I'll bring some to her.
- You'd better.
- Right.
Let's clean this up, yeah?
- I can do it by myself.
- Don't be shy.
Genichi, the guy living below,
how are things with him?
Sometimes I hear him playing the guitar.
Think it's noisy?
Not really.
Aren't his songs amazing?
I don't know.
He was once offered the chance to debut.
Really?
As a musician, that is.
I'm proud of him as a friend.
Take care. Say hi to your parents for me.
Okay.
- Thanks. See you.
- See you.
Wanna try grilling the shishamo again?
If you make a hole like this
before grilling,
they won’t explode.
- Like this?
- Yes.
I got a call from Sakuta.
- About the other day?
- It's about another matter.
The one with Mr. Matsu from the police.
Apparently there’s a meeting with him,
you, me, and your teacher.
Why are the police involved?
Is it about your mom or dad?
Something like that.
It's going to be next Tuesday,
6 p.m., at school.
We’ll tell them the truth
- and get some advice from your teacher.
- No!
I absolutely don't wanna.
I won't go then.
Look, could you tell me what happened?
About the incident, the police, the money…
I don’t know anything.
So, please, give me the rundown.
Okay!
I’ll tell you everything,
only if you'll pretend to be my parent.
- Now that's--
- Please!
Or you can just listen
and think about it for now.
- Well yeah, I'll think about it, but…
- You will?
That's not what I meant.
- I'll go and get ready.
- Get ready?
Oh, and before I forget. This.
CAREER SHEET
He said to submit it.
Ever filled one out before?
Well, yeah.
What did you write
when you were in middle school?
Musician.
Makes sense.
You like music.
You don’t have anything you like?
I don't know.
I see.
Okay, let’s eat.
- Thanks for the meal.
- Not at all.
It's tasty.
I'm glad to hear that.
Fifty-five minutes
to Zenpukuji Middle School.
So, I need to wake up at 5 a.m.?
Today’s place to sleep
Is on a park bench
Sleeping in cramped spots
Is what you're used to
Tomorrow’s place will be in a car
Fallen
Leaves will wrap you up
Hang in there, me.
No home
Oh, no home
The vast sky
Is your roof
The day after tomorrow…
Let's go look for your new home
- Bye.
Bye.
Will you have your career sheet
ready by Tuesday?
- Yes.
- This time, no blanks, okay?
Okay.
Are you getting along well with your dad?
He grilled shishamo for me.
He also taught me
how to prevent them from exploding.
- They explode?
- With a bang.
Please be careful too.
Shishamo… explode?
PRENUPTIAL AGREEMENT
Uh…
Who's this "party A"?
It refers to that guy.
And "party B" is you.
Then, why can't he write "me" and "you"?
- You're right.
- Kinda stupid, huh?
Adults are so lame!
31,500,000 YEN
Coming.
I'm ready.
Okay, let’s read through this together.
Parent-Child Contract.
PARENT-CHILD CONTRACT
From this point forward, Hotaru Kusunoki,
hereafter referred to as "Party A",
and Genichi Hatano,
hereafter referred to as "Party B",
agree to enter
into the following terms
of a parent-child contract,
hereafter referred to as "this Contract".
Now, hold on. What is this?
It's a contract.
You've got to be joking…
You can sign at the end.
- Article One…
- Wait!
You’d think about it, right?
Well, yeah. But…
I’ll tell you everything,
so please listen till the end.
Okay.
Article One. Purpose.
Under all circumstances, Party A
and Party B shall support one another
and strive to maintain a harmonious
pretend parent-child relationship.
The parties enter
into this agreement for this purpose.
Article Two. Agreement.
Party A and Party B
hereby agree on October 20th,
2025, to enter
into a parent-child contract.
Article Three. About Party A. First,
Party A was born on August 26,
2010, 15 years old.
Third-year student
at Zenpukuji Middle School, Class 4.
Second, they currently reside
at Inokashira Apartments,
Room 206.
Three, their father, Jin Ichigaya,
divorced when Party A was nine
and has since left home.
He remarried and started a new family,
so he’s not someone they can rely on.
That was the man from the crepe place?
I actually wanted him to come
to my parent-teacher conference,
but it was apparently
inconvenient for him.
I don’t matter to him anymore.
- Anyway, moving on.
- Uh, okay.
Four, Party A’s mother, Tomoe Kusunoki,
is currently wanted for embezzlement
from her company and is on the run.
She stole money and is on the run.
Since then, I’ve been on my own.
MOM
- Hello?
- Morning, Hotaru.
Mom?
Listen, I won’t be coming home
for a while.
I’m sorry.
There’s a bankbook on the desk.
For the time being,
use that money carefully, okay?
With the landlady,
I left a suitcase.
What’s inside belongs to us.
Us?
Until I'm back,
I’m leaving it in your care. I'll be back.
Okay.
But not long after that, the police came.
They said my mom stole money and ran off
and asked if I knew where she was.
Like I'd believe that, right?
But they kept asking and asking,
and it started to sound like it was true.
The police searched the apartment,
looking for the money.
It used to be just me and Mom
living there,
but little by little, it started to feel
like someone else’s home.
Soon after, someone
from the child guidance center came.
Regarding your situation going forward…
Since you can’t live alone,
if your dad or relatives
can't take you in,
we’ll need to find a facility for you.
I'm good.
My mom said on the phone
that she’d only be gone for a while.
So,
she’ll come back eventually.
I’ll stay here and wait.
I understand how you feel,
but for now, let’s head
to the facility, okay?
Ms. Kusunoki?
My dad.
My dad who left after the divorce.
He saw the news and called.
He said he’s coming back.
So,
I do have a guardian.
I'll be fine.
I lied.
Surprisingly, she believed me.
I didn’t have to go to the facility.
After that, I received the suitcase
from the landlady.
It seems she had just been
holding on to it for me.
Then, when I opened it…
One…
two…
three…
32 million 261 thousand and 570 yen…
ESTIMATED EMBEZZLED FUNDS 32,261,570 YEN
For the time being, I buried the suitcase
in the yard, so no one would find it.
For quite some time, the police
and the child guidance people
would drop by to check on me,
but I just pretended not to be home.
Since my phone is cut off,
this is the only place anyone
could find me.
Not that anyone does.
So, I kept living by myself,
making sure nobody knows about it.
I even lied to my school
- and went about my classes as usual, but…
- Here.
We wrote this for you.
WE’RE STILL FRIENDS!
EVERYONE LIKES YOU!
- I don't want it.
- Why?
Just act like you usually do around me.
- But we saw the news--
- I don't need it!
- It's our heartfelt--
- I said I don't need it!
Isn't that mean?
Everyone kept looking at me with pity,
and I really hated it.
I feel at ease in Toyoko.
I can talk about anything there.
No one treats me like I’m different.
When I told them that my mom
embezzled money, they just laughed it off.
They found it amusing and wild.
They didn’t put up walls
like the kids at school did.
I felt comfortable there. But…
with things like student-parent meetings,
and the meeting tomorrow,
it’s getting harder without a dad lately.
That’s why…
I need someone to pretend to be my parent.
That's the gist of my situation.
Article Four. Payment.
As compensation, Party A shall pay Party B
32,261,570 yen
for entering this contract.
Article Five. Confidentiality.
Both parties shall keep
this contract strictly confidential
and may not disclose it to any third party
without prior consent.
Article Six. Promises.
Both Party A and Party B
agree not to lie to each other.
That’s all.
PARTY A, PARTY B
Please sign here.
In any case, I just want to wait
for my mom here.
I know she didn’t do it.
There must be a reason.
It's just half a year more
until I graduate.
I’ll take care of my own living.
I just need you to act the part sometimes.
So, please.
Hey…
Even if you do manage
to graduate, what then?
I don't know.
You can’t keep living alone here.
I can!
Playing pretend won’t last long.
I'll make sure it does!
You can wait for your mom, sure.
But there has to be another way.
Is there?
In any case, tomorrow,
let’s tell your teacher and the police
- the truth, okay?
- Forget it. We're done here.
Hey, wait!
I’VE LIKED YOU FOR A LONG TIME
MEET ME BEHIND THE GYM ON MONDAY
ELECTRICITY: 3,762 YEN; GAS: 1,486 YEN
WATER: 1,774 YEN
PHONE BILL, FOOD AND TRAIN FARE…
- A minute ago…
- You were sleeping.
Kusunoki.
After class, come to the reception room
on the second floor.
Okay.
Did your dad say he'll be late?
Sorry for being late.
I couldn't quite find my way here.
We've been expecting you.
This is police officer…
I'm Matsu. Nice to meet you.
Thank you
- for taking care of my daughter.
- Huh?
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Today, we’d like to go over
Hotaru’s future living arrangements
and have you, her dad,
to review and confirm them.
- Okay.
- Together with the school
and the child guidance center,
we, as the police, want to coordinate
and support her life going forward.
Right.
Please support Ms. Hotaru
until she's at the age to live on her own.
- I understand.
- Okay.
To start things off, could you please
tell us your name once again?
Genichi Hatano.
Oops…
Hatano?
That’s different from the name Ms. Hotaru
mentioned in the previous meeting.
What's going on?
Uh…
That’s my name after remarriage.
Your first name is different too.
Didn’t you say, "Genichi"?
I m-misspoke. That’s… Well, um…
my stage name.
- Stage name?
- What?
Yes. I used to aim to be a musician.
I didn't manage to debut, but I was close.
Sometimes I still use that name.
It kinda stuck with me.
Besides, in name fortune-telling,
"Genichi Hatano" supposedly brings
better luck, so…
- Wait, so your real name is different?
- Oh,
my real name?
It's…
Jin Ichigaya.
Mr. Jin Ichigaya…
Your stage name is Genichi Hatano?
True, it has a ring to it.
But Jin Ichigaya
also sounds like
a talented actor's name, right?
- Well, yeah…
- Right?
You're hurting Dad's feelings.
I'm sorry.
And what's the status between you
and her mom, Tomoe Kusunoki?
When she was nine,
we divorced, and I haven’t seen her since.
And both of you are now living together.
Yes, that's right.
As to why you hadn’t been in touch
all this time,
was there perhaps some reason?
I just wasn't aware of anything,
whether about the case
or about what was going on.
But she told me everything.
Even the painful things,
she shared it all…
So, I want her
to focus not on daily stuff, meals,
or even money,
but on what she likes, who she likes…
I want her to be preoccupied
with things like that as much as possible.
That’s why
I decided
to be a father to her.
One more time, I mean.
Very well.
So, her daily life seems fine.
Next, a few questions about the case.
I'll go get my bag from class.
I'll be taking my leave now.
- I’ll see you to the exit.
- Thank you. It's fine.
Well then.
I didn't know Hatano was your stage name.
Oh, sorry.
But you can still call me Hatano. Ah…
Sorry.
Um, so now, where are you…
Spending the night in your car, I meant.
At a roadside station.
Hotaru told me everything.
I see.
I thought I’d play the role of her dad.
Sure, I'll leave things to you.
What, you're not going to stop me?
Do you want me to?
‪Well, I’m doing something
‪I probably shouldn’t, right?
Yeah, pretty much.
Right?
- But you've already decided, right?
- Yes.
- Good evening.
- Hello.
This is her middle school
homeroom teacher, Mr. Sakuta.
I'm the landlady, Inokashira.
I'm Sakuta. Sorry for the sudden request.
No worries.
I'd appreciate it if you'd allow me
to park my car here for a while.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
Sorry about this all of the sudden.
Not at all.
You don't have to sleep in your car.
We have plenty of vacant rooms.
- She's right.
- Oh, no.
Living in the same building
as a student would be a little…
Then, feel free to use the yard.
Thank you.
- Well then.
- See you.
Sorry about this. Once I find a place,
I’ll move out immediately.
No rush.
Oh, and your lost item.
I'm talking about your Santa sock.
I tried searching for it,
but it was nowhere to be found.
It's important to you, right?
- I'll try looking for it again.
- Sorry.
I already found it.
Oh, I see. That's great.
- I'll be heading back.
- Okay.
See you.
May I come in?
Why did you introduce him to this place?
He seemed troubled.
If he finds out I live upstairs,
it’ll be bad.
Oh, right.
Don't give me that.
I'm sorry.
- Hey, do you want to eat?
- No.
Come to think about it, isn't it weird
that gays have kids to begin with?
No, some people are married to women too.
And the stage name part…
I pulled that off pretty slick, didn't I?
That was really forced.
Also, how did you even know my dad's name…
or the details of his divorce?
I thought they’d ask,
so I memorized everything in the notebook.
So, does that mean you agree
to the contract?
Just to be clear, I don’t need the money.
- That's not negotiable.
- What?
A contract needs to have consideration.
I really don't need it.
You can just hold on to it for now.
Huh?
PARTY A, PARTY B
Okay then, sign here.
PARTY A: HOTARU KUSUNOKI
PARTY B: GENICHI HATANO
What kind of house are you buying?
Not buying.
I can choose not to use it, right?
Well, yeah.
Okay now, I’ll whip up something simple.
Right away, there's something
I need advice from you as my dad.
What is it?
CAREER SHEET
I've got to submit this.
Haven't you filled it up already?
I'm not sure what to write.
- Any high school you'd like to go to?
- No.
Are there any jobs you'd like to do then?
No.
Why did you quit being a musician?
Here.
You were good enough to debut, right?
It wasn’t because I was good at singing.
It was because I was gay.
They wanted me to sing
in a tight tank top,
speaking all campy, like I never do.
They said it wouldn’t
be newsworthy enough otherwise.
If I hadn’t refused,
maybe I could’ve become
a professional musician.
- Do you have any more shishamo?
- What, you want more?
No, let’s send it to the person
who said that.
And tell them that they don’t have
to poke holes in it.
A shishamo bomb. Let's send it to them.
Even I know that’s a mean thing to say.
You don't have to do that for me.
Have you come to hate singing?
I’ve always loved it.
I thought about quitting.
Every time I see my guitar,
it reminds me of that tight tank top,
and it's annoying.
But eventually, I realized that singing
is something I still loved.
That’s what love feels like, I guess.
What's that?
I guess I’m just thinking
about it unconsciously…
It feels like living the moment together.
I can’t go back
to who I was before meeting them.
Something like that.
What are we talking about?
Who's them?
Sorry, my bad.
Do you have someone you like?
No…
Why do you ask?
No reason.
- Maybe Santa Claus?
- Yeah, right.
Oh, no, no!
Really?
What's with that?
How nice of you to have
a lot of things you love.
I don’t have any, and I don’t understand.
You’ll find it.
- Are you sure?
- Eventually. That's for sure.
One or two things,
definitely.
I’VE LIKED YOU FOR A LONG TIME
MEET ME AFTER SCHOOL ON MONDAY
I forgot about this.
Oh man.
This is Saku's…
After the beep tone,
please leave your name and message.
Hello, Mom? You've gotta hear this.
My future self is always something
I've never been able to imagine.
Like myself in high school.
Or working…
- Good morning.
- What?
- I forgot to submit this yesterday.
- Okay.
- But
my future self finding something
that I love
is what I could slightly imagine.
It sounds pretty fulfilling, huh?
Did you ever have something
you loved, Mom?
Something you wanted to do?
Tell me when you return, yeah?
Okay, bye.
- This is my first time!
- That you reeled in a fish?
No, fishing itself.
You're missing out on life!
This is really fun!
I think I might like it.
Here goes!
You dropped this.
You dropped this!
Thank you.
Embezzlement of 30 million yen?
A female employee is currently on the run.
Subtitle translation by: Jeffery